welcome to junket town
cyborgs are welcomed with open arms in
junket ow
I'm sorry home it's not the Chancellor
but the price is right
I've been all around the world there is
no way that compares to home
treasure secured trolley loaded they'll
never suspect a thing
one last time we take this innocent pile
of ill-gotten treasure to the scrapyard
reveal it to the Queen then BOOM
I'm field advantage you know what do you
think of that your majesty
there's no place like home
maybe don't
only other place I can get some decent
Chinese food
time to pay off the Queen this is not a
good time
let Russia never repeat the mistakes of
this country
during the braver or dumber than you
look to come back here is junk rat you
know better than to show your face
around here Mako
only place for on Nixon junker town is
on the scrapheap consider yourself
warned